okay so this list is going around these internets and this is disrespectful all tyler perry movies
i understand the help is not a black movie for color girls i get it we should just keep it to
the stage but color purple come on now come on now all my life i had to fight it's gonna rain on your
head oh sofia home now sofia home now until you do right by me everything you gonna do gonna fail
you sure is ugly my children in africa i know that no film that had all of them quotables is one that
we're gonna consider one of the worst movies of all time and i know y'all will send them quotes with me
and i know you're gonna drop these quotes in the comments that's the beauty of black culture and we
gonna be celebrating all of that black culture at smart funny and black in la at the novo on may 18th
get your tickets at amandaseals.com because we back they trying to shut blackness down but baby
we gonna be lifting it up be ugly but i'm here